odfl.com 2015-06-22

# Privacy Policy

#### Our Commitment

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Old Dominion Freight Line, Inc. ("ODFL" or "we") collects information from users ("User" or "you") of ODFL's website (together with the websites we maintain at [www.odfl.com](http://www.odfl.com/), [www.odpromises.com](http://www.odpromises.com/), [www.ODFL4me](http://www.odfl4me/) the "Website"). We at ODFL respect your concerns about privacy and are committed to maintaining the confidentiality, integrity, and security of your personal information. This Privacy Policy describes the types of personal information we collect about a User, how we may use the information and with whom we may share the information. The Privacy Policy also describes the measures we take to safeguard your personal information. In addition, this Privacy Policy will provide you with information to (i) change the personal information we maintain about you, (ii) withdraw consent you previously provided to us, (iii) refrain from receiving certain communications, and (iv) answer questions you may have about our Privacy Policy. 

#### Terms and Conditions

By accessing or using this Website in any manner, you agree to be bound by ODFL's Terms and Conditions (the "Agreement"). Please read the Agreement carefully. If you do not accept all of the terms and conditions contained in or incorporated by reference into the Agreement, please do not use this Website.

## Information We Collect

#### Personal Identification Information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our Website, register, submit or post information on our Website, request a service, respond to a survey, fill out a form, or participate in any of ODFL's events, promotions, activities, services, or other offers we make available on our Website. However, we collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us.

More specifically, Users may be asked for individual name and business contact information, company name, email address, postal mailing address, phone and fax number, ODFL account number, freight information, freight recipient's contact information, ODFL username and password to access ODFL's Website and resources, social media handles, payment information, and government identification numbers as required in certain circumstances.

Users may always refuse to supply personal identification information, though it may prevent them from participating in and accessing certain Website related events, promotions, activities, services, or other offers. For example, registering would give Users access to ODFL4me's enhanced tracing, customizable reports, document review, interactive bill of lading, customized rate estimates for the User's specific pricing program, and much more. 

#### Non-Personal Identification Information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Website. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users' means of connection to our Website, such as the operating system, the Internet service provider and other similar information. 

## Collection and Treatment of Information

#### Web Browser Cookies and Internet Tags

Our Website may automate the collection of User information by using "cookies" (a text file that websites send to a visitor's computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify the visitor's browser or to store information or settings in the browser) and/or "internet tags" (these link web pages to web servers and their cookies and may be used to transmit information collected through cookies back to a web server) to obtain "clickstream data" (User-generated data created while browsing a website). The User information we collect via these automated processes include IP address, browser characteristics, User's operating system, referring URLs, and information on User's actions taken on our Website. ODFL may also link certain data elements with other information we have obtained about you to let us know, for example, whether you have opened an account with us or contacted us before. We also may use third-party website analytics tools that collect information about User traffic at our Website. Your browser may tell you how to be notified when you receive certain types of cookies and how to restrict them. We believe that cookies and internet tags provide a safe and secure way to improve the usability of the Website. 

#### How User's Personal Information is Collected

OD collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:  

  1. Administer content, promotion, survey or other Website features
  2. Communicate about, and administer your participation in, special events, programs, surveys, contests, sweepstakes, and other offers or promotions
  3. Comply with all applicable legal requirements and our policies
  4. Deliver pertinent emails and other marketing materials
  5. Enable User to interact and communicate with ODFL through ODFL's social media platforms
  6. Enhance our Website
  7. Establish and manage User's ODFL account
  8. Improve our customer service
  9. Offer products and services ODFL believes may interest User
  10. Operate, evaluate and improve our business (including developing new products and services; managing our communications; determining the effectiveness of our sales, marketing and advertising; analyzing and enhancing our products, services and Website; and performing accounting, auditing, billing, reconciliation and collection activities)
  11. Perform data analyses (including market and consumer search, trend analysis, financial analysis, and anonymization of personal information)
  12. Personalize user experience
  13. Pick up, deliver and track shipments
  14. Process and collect payments
  15. Process and guide transactions
  16. Protect against, identify and prevent fraud and other criminal activity, claims and other liabilities
  17. Provide products and services requested by User (i.e., tracking capabilities)
  18. Provide timely responses to Users in connection with any of our services
  19. Respond and support Users and communicate with User regarding requests, questions and comments

In addition, ODFL uses information collected online through cookies, internet tags and other automated means for purposes such as diagnosing technical and service problems, administering our Website, identifying Users of our Website, and gathering demographic information about our Users. We use clickstream data to determine how much time Users spend on web pages of our Website, how users navigate through our Website, and how we may tailor our Website to better meet the needs of our Users. We also may use the information we obtain about Users in other ways for which we provide specific notice at the time of collection. 

#### Sharing User's Personal Information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users' personal identification information to others except as described in this Privacy Policy. To perform our services, we share shipping information with certain third parties. These third parties are authorized to use the information only as needed to perform services on ODFL's behalf or to comply with legal requirements.

We also may disclose information about User (i) if we are required to do so by law, regulation or legal process (such as a court order or subpoena), (ii) in response to requests by government agencies, such as law enforcement authorities, or (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity. We reserve the right to transfer any information we have about the User in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets (including in the event of a reorganization, dissolution or liquidation).

#### How ODFL Protects User's Personal Information

We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect User's personal information against accidental, unlawful or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure or use. In addition, we also implement appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Website. If ODFL collects account information for payment or credit, ODFL will use the information only to complete the task for which the account information was offered. ODFL will also take security measures to protect such information.

#### Third Party Links

ODFL's Website may contain links to websites operated by parties other than ODFL. Such links are provided for your reference and convenience only. We do not control such websites and are not responsible for their contents or the privacy policies or other practices of such websites. Our inclusion of links to such websites does not imply any endorsement of the material on such websites or any association with their operators. Further, it is up to the User to take precautions to ensure that whatever links the User selects or software the User downloads (whether from this Website or other websites) is free of such items as viruses, worms, trojan horses, defects and other items of a destructive nature. These websites and services may have their own privacy policies, which the User will be subject to upon linking to the third party's website. ODFL strongly recommends that User review the third party's terms and policies. 

#### Compliance With Children's Online Privacy Protection Act

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Website from those we actually know are under the age of 13, and no part of our Website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

#### Changes to This Privacy Policy

ODFL has the discretion to update this Privacy Policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

#### Your Acceptance of These Terms

By using this Website, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the Privacy Policy, please do not use our Website. Your continued use of the Website will be deemed your acceptance of the Privacy Policy, and any subsequent use by you of this Website following changes to any portion of the Privacy Policy shall constitute your acceptance of all such changes

#### User's Choice to Opt-Out, Amend or Access Personal Information 

User may choose not to receive marketing email communications from us by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link in our marketing emails. You also may ask us not to send you other marketing communications by contacting us as specified in the "How To Contact ODFL" section below, and we will honor your request. Consistent with the choices available in the "Sharing User's Personal Information" section, you may withdraw your consent by contacting us as indicated below. In addition, as required by law, you may object at any time on legitimate grounds and free of charge to the processing of your personal information, and we will apply your preferences going forward.

Subject to applicable law, you may obtain a copy of personal information we maintain about you or you may update or correct inaccuracies in that information through your ODFL account at [www.ODFL.com](http://www.odfl.com/). To help protect your privacy and maintain security, we will take steps to verify your identity before granting you access to the information. In addition, if you believe that personal information we maintain about you is inaccurate, subject to applicable law, you may have the right to request that we correct or amend the information by contacting us as indicated below. 

#### How to Contact ODFL

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, or your dealings with this Website, please contact us:

  1. By telephone at 1-800-235-5569
  2. By email request to [Webmaster@odfl.com](mailto:%57%65%62%6D%61%73%74%65%72%40%6F%64%66%6C%2E%63%6F%6D)

##### This Privacy Policy was last updated on April 3, 2012.
